Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

Who we are
----------

We are Satoshi Coffee Co. and our website address is: https://sats.coffee. We pride ourselves in limiting the amount of data we collect as you will see in our privacy policy below.

We do not track you and do not actively use advanced website analytics software.

Comments
--------

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Your Data and Cookies
---------------------

If you opt-in to creating an account for the Coffee Club, or for convenience in ordering in the future, we save the name you provide, an email address or nostr npub, and any other information you provide both in your account and with cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

Embedded content from other websites
------------------------------------

All pages on this site may include embedded content (e.g. BlockClock, images, BTC chart, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

Who we share your data with
---------------------------

We do not share your data with anyone.

If you request a password reset, your IP address will be included in the reset email. Additional data is required for shipping coffee although we don’t KYC you to purchase coffee. You can provide any pseudonym, a burner email, an address forwarder, a PO Box, etc. and use the lightning network and/or on-chain bitcoin to buy your coffee.

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store as minimal as possible data including the information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

For any purchases, we delete personal details such as name, address, etc. after six (6) months, unless you are enrolled in the Coffee Club. During the time required by law, will keep a record of the purchase transaction details, which will include the normal bitcoin and/or lightning transaction headers.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. Other than that, we don’t send your data to anyone or any company.

* * *

PGP: 2EE3 5C29 41D5 4C9E 9E2D C908 33A3 9346 82DD 9E18  

@ 2023

==========================================
